Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Political Surveys, undated, 1936-1969
  - Subseries A: Crossley Inc., undated, 1936-1967
    - Unidentified: New Jersey State presidential attitutdes study, 1952 March (Box 22:, Folder 1253)
    - Unidentified: New Hampshire State voting preferences post-primary research study, 1952 April (Box 22:, Folder 1254)
    - Unidentified: Oregon State voting preferences study, 1952 April (Box 22:, Folder 1255)
  - Subseries B: Various, undated, 1943-1969
    - Albany, NY: Department of Taxation and Finance: Attitutdes toward New York State lottery survey, 1967 October (Box 22:, Folder 1256)
    - Brock, William E.: Tennessee State gubernatorial telephone recontact survey, 1966 April (Box 22:, Folder 1257)
    - Buffalo Evening News: Erie County, NY Presidential campaign survey, 1968 October (Box 22:, Folder 1258)
    - [Cahill for Governor]: New Jersey State attitutdes on issues and gubernatorial candidates survey, 1969 July (Box 22:, Folder 1259)
    - [Cahill for Governor]: New Jersey State opinion on gubernatorial candidates survey, 1969 September (Box 22:, Folder 1260)
    - [Cahill for Governor]: New Jersey State opinion on gubernatorial candidates survey, 1969 October (Box 22:, Folder 1261)
    - Democratic National Committee: L. B. Johnson popularity during 1968 presidential election, 1967 June - 1968 June (Box 22:, Folder 1262)
    - Democratic National Committee: L. B. Johnson popularity during 1968 presidential election, 1967 August - November (Box 22:, Folder 1263)
    - Democratic National Committee: L. B. Johnson popularity during 1968 presidential election, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1664-1265)
    - Democratic National Committee: National attitudes toward L. B. Johnson administration, 1967 August (Box 22:, Folder 1266)
    - Democratic National Committee: National attitudes toward L. B. Johnson administration, 1967 September (Box 22:, Folder 1267)
    - [ Democratic National Committee]: New York State public opinion survey on Johnson presidential campaign, 1967 September (Box 22:, Folder 1268)
    - [ Democratic National Committee]: California State trial heats survey, 1967 October (Box 22:, Folder 1269)
    - Democratic National Committee: National attitudes toward L. B. Johnson administration, 1967 October (Box 22:, Folder 1270)
    - [ Democratic National Committee]: Pennsylvania State trial heats survey, 1967 October (Box 22:, Folder 1271)
    - [ Democratic National Committee]: Stafford County, NH trial heats survey, 1967 October (Box 22:, Folder 1272)
    - First National Bank: Tennessee State political attitudes survey, 1966 January (Box 22:, Folder 1273)
    - First National Bank: Tennessee State public opinion survey, 1966 September (Box 22:, Folder 1274)
    - Indiana Republican State Central Committee: Indiana State political opinion survey, 1966 August (Box 22:, Folder 1275)
    - Jack Tinker & Partners, Inc.: Three City flash telephone survey, 1968 May (Box 23:, Folder 1276)
    - Jack Tinker & Partners, Inc.: Rockefeller for President advertising campaign survey, 1968 July (Box 23:, Folder 1277)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Political opinion survey, 1964 April (Box 23:, Folder 1278)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Political opinion survey, 1964 August (Box 23:, Folder 1279)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Political opinion survey, 1964 December (Box 23:, Folder 1280)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Attitudes on issues, parties, legislature and candidates for Governor survey, 1965 June (Box 23:, Folder 1281)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Attitudes toward potential senatorial candidates telephone survey, 1966 May (Box 23:, Folder 1282-1283)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Congressional campaign issues and standing of potential senatorial candidates survey, 1966 May (Box 23:, Folder 1284)
    - New Jersey Democratic State Committee: Public opinion survey, 1967 July (Box 23:, Folder 1285)
    - Oshry, Harold G>: Indiana state political opinion survey, 1964 April (Box 23:, Folder 1286)
    - People for Rockefeller and Rockefeller for President: Rockefeller Presidential campaign public opinion survey, 1968 July (Box 23:, Folder 1287)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin: Pennsylvania public opinion survey #1, 1966 August (Box 23:, Folder 1288)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin: Pennsylvania public opinion survey #2, 1966 October (Box 23:, Folder 1289)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin: Pennsylvania public opinion survey #3, 1966 october (Box 23:, Folder 1290)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin: Philadelphia mayoralty survey #1, 1967 September (Box 23:, Folder 1291)
    - Philadelphia Bulletin: Philadelphia mayoralty survey #2, 1967 October (Box 23:, Folder 1292)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: General Administrative, 1963-1965 (Box 23:, Folder 1293)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: General Administrative, 1966-1969 (Box 23:, Folder 1294)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: Stock transfer correspondence, 1962 December - 1969 February (Box 23:, Folder 1295)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: Stick transfer notes and financials, undated (Box 23:, Folder 1296)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: Promotional materials, undated (Box 23:, Folder 1297)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: Charles E. Roll articles, undated (Box 23:, Folder 1298)
    - Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc.: Gallup Poll questionnaires for PSA, Inc. surveys, 1963 February - 1968 (Box 23:, Folder 1299)
    - Rrepublican City campaign committee: Political attitude survey, New York, NY, 1965 October (Box 23:, Folder 1300)
    - Research Council, Inc.: National public opinion telephone survey, 1966 January (Box 23:, Folder 1301)
    - Research Council, Inc.: National public opinion telephone survey #2, 1966 January (Box 23:, Folder 1302)
    - Research Council, Inc.: National public opinion telephone survey #3, 1966 January (Box 23:, Folder 1303)
    - R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Co.: National cigarette smokers' attitude toward Yugoslavia n tobacco survey, 1967 May (Box 23:, Folder 1304)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York Staet water pollution study report, undated (Box 24:, Folder 1305)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Field materials, undated (Box 24:, Folder 1306)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc. letters of agreement, 1963 January (Box 24:, Folder 1307)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Governor Rockefeller as presidential candidate survey, 1963 January (Box 24:, Folder 1308)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: First New York study, 1963 February (Box 24:, Folder 1309)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Milwaukee, WI survey, 1963 [March] (Box 24:, Folder 1310)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Second New York study, 1963 [March] (Box 24:, Folder 1311)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Special Gallup Poll survey, 1963 [March] (Box 24:, Folder 1312)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Cincinnati, OH, 1963 April-May (Box 24:, Folder 1313)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Special trial heats survey, 1963 May (Box 24:, Folder 1314)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Trust and confidence in Kennedy administration survey, 1963 [July] (Box 24:, Folder 1315)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Rockefeller remarriage and domestic and international issues survey, 1963 February (Box 24:, Folder 1316)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Special Rockefeller remarriage effect survey correspondence, 1963 October (Box 24:, Folder 1317)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Trust and confidence in Kennedy Administration survey, 1963 October (Box 24:, Folder 1318)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Upstate New York telephone survey, 1963 October (Box 24:, Folder 1319)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New Hampshire political opinion survey, 1963 November (Box 24:, Folder 1320)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Political survey of New York State, 1963 November (Box 24:, Folder 1321)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Trust and confidence in Goldwater survey, 1963 November (Box 24:, Folder 1322)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National issues survey, 1963 December (Box 24:, Folder 1323)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Opinions of GOP primary electrion voters in New Hampshire survey, 1963 December (Box 24:, Folder 1324)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: GOP presidential choice survey, 1964 January (Box 24:, Folder 1325)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New Hampshire diagnotic study, 1964 January (Box 24:, Folder 1326)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Special West Virginia survey, 1964 January (Box 24:, Folder 1327)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: California telephone survey, 1964 February (Box 24:, Folder 1328)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Special Maryland state poll, 1964 February (Box 24:, Folder 1329)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Supplementary issues survey, 1964 February (Box 24:, Folder 1330)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New Jersey telephone survey, 1964 March (Box 24:, Folder 1331)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York telephone survey, 1964 March (Box 24:, Folder 1332)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Opinions of GOP primary election voters, 1964 March (Box 24:, Folder 1333)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Opinions of GOP primary election voters, 1964 March (Box 24:, Folder 1334)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Trust and confidence in Johnson survey, 1964 March (Box 24:, Folder 1335)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Oregon diagnostic study, 1964 April (Box 24:, Folder 1336)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Re-survey of likely GOP primary voters in Oregon, 1964 April (Box 24:, Folder 1337)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Final California primary study, 1964 [May] (Box 24:, Folder 1338)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Re-survey of likely GOP primary voters in California, 1964 May (Box 24:, Folder 1339)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State attitude study, 1964 December (Box 24:, Folder 1340-1341)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Depth interviewing of selected New York State political representatives survey correspondence, 1965 June - August (Box 24:, Folder 1342)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: POlitical attitudes in New York State survey, 1965 July (Box 24:, Folder 1343)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York flash telephone survey, 1965 September (Box 24:, Folder 1344)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: POlitical attitudes in New York State, 1965 December (Box 24:, Folder 1345)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York City flash telephone survey, 1966 March (Box 24:, Folder 1346)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State political attitude survey, 1966 April (Box 24:, Folder 1347)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Film exposure test and attitutdes towward Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller study, 1966 June (Box 24:, Folder 1348)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York City flash telephone survey, 1966 June (Box 24:, Folder 1349)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Hudeson River Valley survey, 1966 August (Box 24:, Folder 1350)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State political attitude survey, 1966 August (Box 24:, Folder 1351)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State candidate standing and campaign issues, 1966 September (Box 24:, Folder 1352)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State candidate standing and campaign issues, 1966 September (Box 24:, Folder 1353)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Excessive campaign spending telephone survey, 1966 october (Box 24:, Folder 1354)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State standings study, 1966 October (Box 25:, Folder 1355-1356)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Rockefeller film exposire survey, 1966 October (Box 25:, Folder 1357)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State candidate standings survey, 1966 November (Box 25:, Folder 1358)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National political survey, 1966 December (Box 25:, Folder 1359)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State public opinion survey, 1967 June (Box 25:, Folder 1360)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State public opinion survey, 1967 June (Box 25:, Folder 1361)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State firearm registration survey, 1967 September (Box 25:, Folder 1362)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State mass transportation bond bill survey, 1967 October (Box 25:, Folder 1363)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State new constitution proposal survey, 1967 October (Box 25:, Folder 1364)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Midwest political interest survey, 1968 January (Box 25:, Folder 1365)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National survey of political attitudes, 1968 February (Box 25:, Folder 1366)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: Attitudes on selected New York State issues survey, 1968 March (Box 25:, Folder 1367)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: West coast political survey: Oregon, 1968 March (Box 25:, Folder 1368)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National flash telephone survey, 1968 May (Box 25:, Folder 1369)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: West coast flash telephone survey: Oregon, 1968 May (Box 25:, Folder 1370)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National attitudes toward presidential candidates survey, 1968 June (Box 25:, Folder 1371)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: National public opinion survey on trust, 1968 July (Box 25:, Folder 1372)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State 25th Congressional district public opinion survey, 1968 October (Box 25:, Folder 1373)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich: New York State survey, 1969 February (Box 25:, Folder 1374)
    - Unidentified: National survey of attitudes, hopes and fears, 1964 September (Box 25:, Folder 1375)
    - Unidentified: National survey of attitudes, hopes and fears, 1964 October (Box 25:, Folder 1376)
    - Unidentified: Political attitude survey: New Jersey, 1965 July (Box 25:, Folder 1377)
    - Unidentified: Political attitude survey: New Jersey, 1965 September (Box 25:, Folder 1378)
    - Unidentified: New York State 28th Congressional district voter population survey, 1966 January (Box 25:, Folder 1379)
- Series III: Socio-Economic Surveys, undated, 1937-1962
  - Agricultural Marketing Service: Fibers in household furnishing study, 1958 November (Box 25:, Folder 1380)
  - American Heritage Foundation and Tide Magazine: Freedom Train campaign test study, Provo, Utah, 1948 March - April (Box 25:, Folder 1381)
  - American Medical Association: Research program proposal, 1949 February - 1951 February (Box 25:, Folder 1382-1383)
  - American Nurses' Association: Opinions of nurses regarding professional associations survey, 1949 January (Box 25:, Folder 1384)
  - Committee for Economic Development: Post-war markets for manufactured goods study, 1945 June (Box 25:, Folder 1385)
  - Economic Research Service: Truck crop production practices study: Virginia counties, 1961 December (Box 25:, Folder 1386)
  - Economic Research Service: Truck crop production practices study: Florida counties, 1962 October (Box 25:, Folder 1387)
  - Edward L. Bernays, et. al.: Experimental study of social attitudes toward prominent families within a town: Auburn, NY, 1948 June (Box 25:, Folder 1388)
  - Federal Security Agency: Effectiveness of Nutrition campaign: South Bend, IN study proposal, 1942 February (Box 25:, Folder 1389)
  - Federal Security Agency: Cross-section record of food requirements: South Bend, IN study, 1942 March (Box 25:, Folder 1390)
  - Federal Security Agency: Public opinion on foods: South Bend, IN nutrition study, 1942 March, May (Box 25:, Folder 1391)
  - Fish and Wildlife Service: National survey of fishing and hunting, 1956 Summer (Box 25:, Folder 1392)
  - Fish and Wildlife Service: National survey of fishing and hunting, 1960 September (Box 25:, Folder 1393)
  - National Conference of Athletic Directors: Impact of television on football game attendance study, 1948 December (Box 25:, Folder 1394)
  - Nation's Business: "Test Tube for unemployment" article, 1937 Octber (Box 25:, Folder 1395)
  - [ Office of Price Administration]: Survey of prices: Indianapolis, IN, 1942 August (Box 25:, Folder 1396)
  - Office of War Information: Comparative price control study proposal, 1942 July (Box 25:, Folder 1397)
  - Outdoor Advertising: Preliminary research program procedure notes, 1958 October (Box 25:, Folder 1398)
  - Passenger Service Improvement Corporation of Philadelphia: Passenger traffic studies proposals, 1963 March (Box 25:, Folder 1399)
  - Press releases concerning racial issues, 1963-1968 (Box 25:, Folder 1400)
  - Princeton Community Chest: Community Chest appraisal study: Princeton, NJ, 1948 August (Box 25:, Folder 1401)
  - Public Health Service: Health behavior and health attitudes study proposal, 1964 June (Box 25:, Folder 1402)
  - Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc.: Annual tipping by apartment house tenants study (Manhattan), 1948 December (Box 25:, Folder 1403)
  - Springfield Community Chest: Public attitude toward social services study: Springfield, MA, 1947 September (Box 25:, Folder 1404)
  - Unidentified: Three city study of war workers, undated (Box 25:, Folder 1405)
  - War Production Board: Surveys of consumer requirements, 1943 December, 1944 April (Box 25:, Folder 1406)
  - War Production Board: Retail supply study, 1944 June (Box 25:, Folder 1407)
- Series IV: International Tensions [Princeton 1917 Project--Self-Determination and Peace: Monitoring Mass Attitudes Project], undated, 1976-1982
  - Background information, undated, 1976-1983 (Box 26:, Folder 1408)
  - Correspondence, 1977 January - 1978 December (Box 26:, Folder 1409)
  - Correspondence, 1979 January - 1983 January (Box 26:, Folder 1410)
  - Funding: Donor records and general notes, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 1411)
  - Conference: Participant papers, 1979 March (Box 26:, Folder 1412)
  - Conference: Press releases and pertinent publications, 1979 March (Box 26:, Folder 1413)
  - Conference: Program materials, 1979 March (Box 26:, Folder 1414)
  - Operational and survey materials, undated, 1978-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 1415)
  - Reference materials, undated, 1977-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 1416)
  - Reference material: Futility of war as an instrument of U.S. foreign policy [ George Gallup], 1970 August (Box 26:, Folder 1417)
  - Reference material: Hoover Institution on war, revolution and peace reports, 1977, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 1418)
  - Reference materials: Princeton University Center for International Studies, 26th Annual report, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 1419)
  - Reference materials: Institute for World Order Peace Money report, 1978 December (Box 26:, Folder 1420)
  - Reference material: Foreign Broadcast Information Service Middle East and North African report, 1979 May (Box 26:, Folder 1421)
  - International Peace Academy: Workshop background information, 1980 June (Box 26:, Folder 1422)
  - International Peace Academy: Workshop correspondence, 1979 October - 1982 November (Box 26:, Folder 1423)
  - International Peace Academy: Workshop program materials, 1980 June (Box 26:, Folder 1424)
  - International Peace Academy: Publications and press releases, 1976-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 1425)
  - Test survey and future development, undated, 1979-1983 (Box 27)
    - Report: Role of the People in Conflict Resolution, 1982
    - "Role of the People in conflict resolution: The Falklands/Malvinas Conflict" paper, AAPOR Conference, 1983
    - Background materials, 1979-1983
    - Notes and Photographs [2 ff], undated
    - National Peace Academy, 1982
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1979-1983
    - United Nations, 1980-1982
    - Clippings, 1982-1983
    - Survey material [Gallup], 1982
    - International Disputes: Test survey, findings among London sample, 1982
    - International Disputes: Test survey, preliminary findings among Uruguay sample, 1982
    - International Disputes: Test survey, findings among Uruguay sample, 1982
    - Gallup Organization, Inc.: Completed survey forms [3 ff], undated, 1982
- Series V: Speeches, undated, 1939-1975
  - Index, undated, 1939-1964 (Box 26)
    - Undated
    - 1939-1944
    - 1945-1946
    - 1947-1948
    - 1949-1950
    - 1952-1955
    - 1957-1967
    - 1968, 1975
    - Notecards, 1943-1968
- Series VI: Correspondence, undated, 1943-1980
  Scope and Contents note
  The correspondence has been foldered in the order in which it was received from the donor. An index accompanied the correspondence and is filed with the materials. The index identifies the author and recipient of the item, institutional affiliation (if any) and date. A note has been added to the index to indicate which of the five folders the specific items may be located, although in some instances the location may be approximate rather than exact.
  - (Box 27)
    - Correspondence index
    - Correspondence, 1943-1980; [5 folders]
- Series VII: Business Organizations, undated, 1926-2002
  - Subseries A: Crossley, Inc. (1926-1954), undated, 1926-2002 (Box 28, OS)
    - Administration, undated, 1926-1969; [7 folders]
      Subjects include: Home office, staff addresses, 20th anniversary party, legal research, radio/magazine study (Broadcast Advertising Bureau (see Series I.A), field staff management and interviewer coverage.
    - Promotion, undated, 1943-1953; [1 oversize item, 5 folders]
      Subjects include: Ratingitis, Exploring with Crossleym radio and sales, proposals in regard to advertising effectiveness.
    - Sampling, undated, 1935-1959
      Subjects include: Papers on sampling theory underlying survey research; Crossley and others.
    - Radio-Graph Corporation and Middletowns, Inc., undated, 1939-1951
      General note
      [Radio set recorder located in Box 35.]
    - Merger with Stewart Dougall & Associates, Inc., undated, 1954-1956
  - Subseries B: Crossley SD Surveys, Inc. (1954-2002), undated, 1933-2002 (Box 29, 32)
    - Administration, 1954-1959
    - Promotion, undated, 1933-1959
    - Reorganization, undated, 1954-1967; [2 folders]
    - Crossley 50th Anniversary, 1976
    - Post 1961 activities, undated, 1954-2002
  - Subseries C: ArchCross Associates, Inc. (1954-1986), undated, 1955-1986
    - Business activities, undated, 1955-1982; [6 folders]
      Subjects include: administration, Political Surveys and Analyses, Inc. [see Series II.B], International tensions projects [see Series IV] and business travel.
    - Dissolution, undated, 1985-1986
- Series VIII: Personal papers, undated, 1930-2002
  - Subseries A: Biographic materials, undated, 1941-1980 (Box 29)
    - Biographical notes, undated, 1941-1980
    - Obituaries, 1985
    - Funeral service and Memorials, 1985-1986
    - Family matters, undated, 1944-1983
  - Subseries B: Unpublished manuscripts, undated, 1950
    - "Memory problems in advertising effectiveness measurement," Senior thesis, Princeton University, 1950 (Box 29)
    - "This research business,", undated (Box 29)
    - "The Computer's Maw,", undated (Box 29)
    - Notes on revision,", undated (Box 29, 32)
    - "The Public Wants,", undated (Box 29)
    - "But nobody ever interviewed me,", undated (Box 30)
  - Subseries C: Organizations, undated, 1949-1987
    - Marketing and advertising groups, undated, 1930-1987; [4 folders] (Box 30)
      Subjects include: Marketing Research Council, American Marketing Association, Advertising Research Foundation, Association of National Advertisers, among others.
    - National Council on Political Polls, undated, 1969-1983; [3 folders] (Box 30)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research, undated, 1955-1986; [2 folders] (Box 30)
    - Roper Public Opinion Research Center, 1965, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Interagency committee on research standards and ethics, undated, 1944-1970; [2 folders] (Box 30)